<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
   <element>
      
      <text>Usually stay near the airport, but this trip we had business on the north side of Balto.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>The traffic is too crazy staying elsewhere.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>This hotel was perfect, the hot breakfast wonderful - recommend getting the breakfast package if there are 2 of you in the room.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>Only hotel in the area with a restaurant and bar.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>This area does not have a whole lot of good restaurants (compared to staying near Columbia or Pikesville or off 83).</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>It is next to White Marsh Mall which is a huge complex of shopping including an Ikea.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>The beds were fabulous - you can adjust your side for firmness.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>It was like most Hilton Garden Inns.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>It was nice, people were pleasant (very), cheap good breakfast ($10), small but nice workout facilities and pool, good rooms/bathrooms.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>Most of all, we appreciated the free shuttle to a mall, plenty of restaurants, Ikea, etc.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>Stayed there one night, December 16, on the way from Norther Virginia to Philadelphia.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>Located about a mile off 95, this place is clean, bright, and welcoming.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>The rooms are large; so is the made-to-order breakfast.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>The bedding is a cut above a Hampton Inn, say.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>All in all, a good stopover, with two caveats.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>Ask for a room not facing the Interstate.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>And have low expectations for the fitness center, a small room with one elliptical and two treadmills.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>I just stayed here last weekend and have already planned to stay here again the night before New Years.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>There is a very warm atmosphere about this inn and I personally think its more like a hotel than an inn.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>They actually have room service from 5-10 which are the same hours as their restaurant.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>This is something I couldn't find elsewhere in the area.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>If anyone reading this knows better...please feel free to educate me :o) Outside of room service hours there is a pantry with both wine and beer available too.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>I took advantage of this given I was in the area visiting my girl friend.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>The chef..I think Patty is her name is really nice, very entertaining and very obviously a hit with the locals.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>Both mornings I had breakfast..more non residents came in for breakfast than residents and the breakfast was delicious.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>Eggs/pancakes etc made to order and plenty of selection.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>The beds are one touch beds which allow adjustment for firmness..I slept like a log..no need for more to be said.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>The stay comes with complimentary access to Bally Fitness/La Fitness (large well equipped gym) within a 2 minute walk from the hotel.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>This hotel will be my hotel of choice for stays in Baltimore for the foreseeable future.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>My mother who is 90 and I stayed one night on our way to Virginia Beach, VA.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>While she can walk-she can't walk far and also needs a bathroom made for handicapped people.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>We stayed in one of those rooms on the first floor.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>It was very helpful for my mom.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>We also had the breakfast buffet.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>It was very reasonably priced and very delicious.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>My brother-in-law who lives in Baltimore recommended this hotel and I will too!</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>Great Place!</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>A fabulous stop.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>Clean, friendly, excellent location, fine amenities.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>The bedding was exceptional.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>I stopped here just for the night on a road trip.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>It was kind of expensive, but the room was very clean and spacious.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>The bed was very comfortable and the bath products were great.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>Since I'm a light sleeper, I asked for a room on the top floor away from vending machine and elevators, and the front desk clerk was very gracious about it.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>I forgot to ask to be on the side away from the interstate, but the room turned out to be on the quiet side anyway.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>I would definitely stay here again if I were in the area.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>Great spot close to shops and dinning but perhaps a bit too close to the highway (if you get on the wrong side of the hotel).</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>My first room was on the side &amp; end closest to Rt 95.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>After the first night, I had to have my room switched because the traffic noise, especially in the early hours (@3AM) was much too loud (tons of truck).</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>The next 3 nights I was on the opite side and end, and all was well.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>The staff was very understanding and helpful in making the switch for me.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>The location was right where we wanted.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>The hotel was very nice overall.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>The main drawback was not of any fault of the hotel, there was a lacrosse tournament in the area so both Saturday and Sunday mornings I was awakened by noise in the hallways.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>I was surprised to see a manual thermostat in the room so it was hard to regulate the air conditioner.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>I also did not like the layout of the bathroom.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>The towel rack was inside the shower and the toilet paper was difficult to reach from the toilet.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>Anyone with young children would have had issues with this.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>We did not use the pool however there was a sign at the desk that there is a 17 person limit and a waiting list at times.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>Super clean.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>Great hotel to stay at.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>We actually stayed here twice in April for family functions, since we were from out of town.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>Great service.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>I have no complaints at all.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>Due to unforeseen circumstances, I found myself looking for a hotel in my area.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>I remembered the few hotels in the White Marsh area and immediately called the Hilton.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>They quoted me a single king bed at $199.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>I then asked for military discount and the room came down to $99.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>What a great surprise.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>Especially since $199 was very high.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>When I got there, I definitely saw why the hotel had higher prices.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>WHAT A GREAT HOTEL!!!!</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>The room had a fridge, microwave, and nice coffee area.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>Great sitting area with a couch and desk.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>The bed was great!</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>It molds to your body and is amazing.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>After a rough day, it was very nice to have such a comfortable place.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>I loved that they also offered free internet.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>If need be, I would stay here again, and I would def recommend to out of town guests.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>BTW, the front desk girl was very friendly and she seemed to genuinely enjoy her hotel and her job.</text>
   </element>
   <element>
      
      <text>Super clean, lots of shops and restaurants within walking distance 15 min from the bay.</text>
   </element>
</root>